- [BILLY] Hello?
- [JORDAN] Hey.
I just called to check if you're okay.
I'm okay.
I don't want to add to your problems.
I just found out
Bea got off the hook again.
What?
Ms. Talia! Ms. Talia!
What are you doing here?
I thought you were in jail!
I've done nothing wrong!
- [BEA] Ms. Talia!
- Billy?
Bea's here, and she's making a scene.
I thought our plan would put her in jail.
- Auntie Pres.
- Oh, Billy! I'm sorry.
- I forgot to call you.
- It's okay.
They said Sir Eric couldn't
come in to work today.
Who paid for it?
Your daughter did.
- She came here?
- Mm.
You were asleep when she visited you.
The bill has been paid, but please,
don't make me your emergency contact
because next time, I won't be coming.
[PRECIOUS]
Your father really is the worst.
He even got you involved in his debts.
I'm not surprised anymore, Auntie Pres.
When I found out that he became
a scammer in Canada,
I already knew that
he was only after money.
[MARJ] You're right!
[BILLY] What are you doing here?
Can you please talk to your people?
Let the world know that I'm a criminal?!
Do you think you're going to scare me?
Enjoy your freedom
because it won't last long.
Oh! And by the way…
Orange looks good on you.
[BILLY] They will officially provide us
our cybersecurity.
Charm, what's wrong?
Ralph's mom sent this.
And now they're questioning me
if they did the right thing
when they invested in us.
But what's worse is,
they're questioning
my relationship with Ralph.
I thought you couldn't get to work today.
By the way,
Billy wanted to give this to you.
Actually, she's already been here twice,
but you just keep missing each other.
Yeah, it's a shame.
[MARIELA] Have some, dear.
It's so luxurious here.
The last time we ate at a place like this
was when your sister Abi got promoted.
And now, it's you.
[CHUCKLES]
That Billy thinks
that she can just treat you
like you're nothing.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
That's why I told you
to just trust me, Ma.
Have faith in me.
Did you just grimace?
Are you disgusted?
Why? Is it illegal to pick your teeth?
Just pour me some wine
before I run out of patience with you.
That's it?
Come on, pour some more.
What about you, Ma?
Pour some for my mom too.
Oh!
- Okay.
- There we go.
- Thank you.
- Ma.
Cheers.
[SQUEALS SOFTLY]
- Cheers.
- Cheers to…
us.
Cheers.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Eat more, Ma.
- Here.
- You too.
This. You dip it like this. Look.
[BEA] Eat up.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
I should be the one handling this, Ma.
It was Benilda Cariño herself
who invited me out for dinner.
What?
Wait, I'm on my way.
I'm going to go there.
[ROWENA] Ralph, son.
You're biased.
Okay? Your girlfriend works
for the company.
Let me be the judge
if you made the right choice
in investing in this shady company.
Shady?
[RALPH] What do you mean, shady?
Ma, the legal issues
are not directly connected to LoveList.
Then let me see for myself, okay?
I appreciate Billy's invitation
so she could clear
her name and the company.
Now, I just want to know if the CEO
of LoveList is a decent woman.
Ma.
Hello, Ma.
Ma, just wait for me outside.
- I'm just going to settle the bill.
- Okay.
Yes, ma'am? Can I help you?
Ah, no. No, it's okay.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hi, miss. Good evening.
- Hi, ma'am. Good evening.
I have a reservation under Billy Cariño.
[WOMAN] Your table will be
ready in a few minutes.
- I'll just check your table.
- Okay. Thank you.
Are you following my daughter?!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC STING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Cat got your tongue?
I'm not following your daughter.
You're trying to start a fight.
Well, face me first.
Excuse me.
When will you leave my daughter alone?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Like I told you before…
it's your daughter you need to talk to.
How dare you?!
Not today.
Ma. Ma!
Let go of my mother.
- Leave my daughter alone!
- [BEA] Ma!
- Ma.
- Karma will get you one day!
I'll be waiting.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why did you stop me?
I was ready to smack her face.
She can't take both of us.
Shh. It's okay. It's done.
Thanks, Ma. Thank you for defending me.
But Billy is mine to handle.
I told you that, right?
I'll handle her.
But Caloy is gone.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's just go home.
[WHEELS SCREECHING]
Come on, let's go.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BEA] Let's go, mister.
Ms. Rowena, thank you so much
for taking the time to meet me.
And I'm sorry about earlier.
[SCOFFS]
- Don't be sorry.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
It just made me realize
that my instinct is never wrong.
My son made the wrong decision
to trust you and your company.
With all due respect, ma'am,
I think your son made
a very wise decision.
[LAUGHS]
Based on what I saw earlier?
Again, I'm sorry you had to see that.
It was a personal matter
that you should not have seen.
Maybe we can just focus on this instead?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
LoveList is up 42 percent
since we launched Happily Ever After.
- Imagine what we can--
- Look.
I know you're doing this
because Charm is your friend.
And while I admire you
for being a good friend,
I also need to be a good mother.
I need to protect my son's well-being.
Okay?
- Billy. Billy, I'm sorry.
- [MOUTHS SILENTLY]
It's okay. I'll handle Mama.
No. It's not okay, Ralph.
We're going to pull out.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
We can't, Mom.
We can. It's covered under the morality
and reputational risk clause
of the contract.
Okay. If that's the case,
I'm pulling out too.
From what? Our business?
You can't.
Your money is our money.
No.
From our family.
All my life, I've just done
whatever you told me.
And that ends now.
- I'm already an adult!
- Then think like one!
This company is not good for you,
especially that girlfriend of yours!
Excuse me, ma'am.
I understand that
you're just looking out for your son.
But have you tried
getting to know Charm personally?
Not just based on what you see
or hear from other people?
I hope you'll also give her a chance.
This meeting
is done.
Don't stay up too late.
We have a board meeting tomorrow.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[RALPH] Billy, I'm sorry.
[BILLY] It's okay.
[RALPH HUFFS]
At Ralph's age,
I can't believe his mom
is still that controlling.
Well, I'd rather have a controlling parent
than one who doesn't care.
Not everyone has a parent
who worries about them.
You have a point.
But there should be a limit.
Of course. But you know,
she does all that
because she loves her son.
Makes you wonder, what if…
What if you had a mom
who was as protective as Ralph's?
Or like Bea's mom.
- Bea?
- Mm-hmm.
I mean, didn't she come after me
because of her daughter?
Bea's lucky to have a mom like that.
She's just unlucky
with her dad. He left her too.
Thank you.
[JORDAN] Mix it up first.
This looks new.
- Billy.
- [JORDAN] Charm.
[BILLY] Charm.
- Ralph.
- Brother.
Billy, thank you.
Because of you,
I finally came to my senses.
Give him credit, Charm.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
From now on,
I will decide for myself.
Yes, but remember,
your mom is just worried about you.
Our goal is for everyone
to understand each other.
Remember what happened
with Melissa's dad and Theo?
But you don't know my mom.
She'll do anything to get her way.
Look, I've been a good son all my life.
But now…
Now, it's time for me
to be a better boyfriend.
I need to make a stand.
I don't care if she gets mad.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you, Ralph.
[CHARM] But Billy's right.
I just want all of us to get along.
Your mother loves you, Ralph.
She will meet you halfway.
That's what parents do…
I mean, most parents will do anything
for their kids, right?
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
["SUGAL" BY BRYAN CHONG PLAYING]
[CLAPPING]
[BOTTLES CLINK]
["SUGAL" CONTINUES]
Give me my five hundred.
Hey, hold on. We're not sure yet.
Well, I'm sure.
Not yet.
Fine. If you say so.
See?
That's your magic.
You're like Cupid.
Mm…
That's why you're perfect for LoveList.
[BILLY] Mm?
[BILLY] Well, I'm not planning
to be Cupid.
It's a hard job.
[BILLY] Do you remember?
I created LoveList
because I didn't want
what happened to me--
To happen again?
Mm-hmm.
And what happened to Mama.
- Cheers.
Wait. Let's take a picture.
I look a mess.
You should've taken it earlier.
Come on, let's take one.
Hmph!
- How do I look?
- You look fine.
Teeth?
- Don't worry.
- Okay.
You're already beautiful. Hurry.
- Give me your phone.
- Why my phone?
- The camera's better.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Ready.
- Yay! They've made up.
- Cheers!
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
That angle makes me look bad.
One more time.
- [PHONE CHIMES]
- Oh, wait.
- Who is this?
- Give it to me.
You're too nosy! [CHUCKLES]
I've already seen it, so just tell me.
Who is it?
Someone I matched with on LoveList.
- Mm-hmm.
- On LoveList?
Mm-hmm.
Is he bothering you?
No, he's not bothering me.
I would've blocked him already if he was.
So,
you like him?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mm.
- Mm.
- [JORDAN] Hmm…
Is that really him?
Maybe he's just a poser.
Are you really working at LoveList?
Yes.
All the accounts on our app
are verified, remember?
- Okay.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Kris is a corporate lawyer.
He graduated in the UK.
He's 32 and already has his own law firm.
He likes to surf.
He has a younger brother
who's a freshman in college.
How's that?
- Wow.
- [BILLY] Wow.
You know a lot about him.
Are you really LoveList's tech lead?
Obviously, I read all of it
on his profile.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I thought you were busy.
So just because I'm busy, I can't date?
Is it forbidden?
And weren't you the one who told me
I needed a distraction?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
If I do find love,
I don't want to call it a distraction.
He should support me more than anyone
so I can stay focused on my goals.
Right? Right.
- Right.
- [BILLY] Mm-hmm.
So, that guy is the one
you're talking about?
[BILLY] Well, let's see.
Why are you asking so many questions?
Are you a lawyer?
Why not?
We don't know this guy.
Look, all I'm saying is,
if you decide to go out
with this Kris guy or…
- [BOTTLES CLINK]
- Easy.
- …whoever.
- Mm-hmm.
Just let me know.
I'm ready to be
your chaperone-slash-bouncer.
I'll think about it.
- You don't want to?
- Mm.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC FADES]
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
- Yay! They've made up.
- Cheers!
- Wait!
- Who is this?
You're too nosy!
I've already seen it,
so just tell me.
Someone I matched with
on LoveList.
Are you feeling ill, Jordan?
A little.
I don't know if it's right
to feel this way about Sir Eric.
Don't you feel that way
about Brandon?
No, this is different.
Please give me a sign
if it's right to feel this way.
You're up early, Ms. Supervisor.
Well, I have to.
Do your best, dear.
I will, like I always do.
[PHONE RINGS]
Kris?
Hi! [GIGGLES]
Oh, you're near?
Okay, I can meet you outside.